One of the biggest benefits of using ROS is that it has
ROS を使用する最大の利点の 1 つは
a really large community of users and developers,
ユーザーと開発者の巨大なコミュニティがあるために
so there's a lot of code that you can use.
利用可能なコードがたくさんあるということです
Let's clone an existing package and add it to our newly created workspace.
ではここで 既存のパッケージのクローンを作成し 新しく作成したワークスペースに追加してみましょう
You'll start by navigating to the source directory.
まず ソースディレクトリに移動します
Then you'll use Git to clone the simple arm package for this lesson from its GitHub repo.
そして Git を使用してGitHub リポジトリからこのレッスンで使用する simple_arm パッケージのクローンを作成します
Don't worry about trying to pause the video to copy the url that I've shown here,
ビデオを一時停止して ここで示す URL をコピーする心配はありません
as it's provided in the text module below.
これは下のテキストモジュールにあります
After the repo is finished cloning,
クローンが作成されたら
you can change the directory to the top level of the ROS workspace and
ROS ワークスペースの最上位ディレクトリに移動し
build the new package using the command catkin-make.
コマンド catkin-make を使用して新たなパッケージを作成します
I have seen an error.
エラーがありますね
"Could not find a package configuration file provided by 'controller_manager.'"
"Could not find a package configuration file provided by 'controller_manager.'"
I happen to know that controller_manager refers to a ROS package from ROS control.
controller_manager は ROS コントロールからの ROS パッケージのことだとわかりました
We can fix this by installing the associated Debian package.
この問題は 関連する Debian パッケージをインストールすることで解決できます
If I didn't already know this,
しかし この知識がない場合は
I would probably have to rely on a Google search to
必要とされる正確なパッケージ名が分からないため
figure out the exact name of the package required.
Google などで検索しなければなりません
OK. Now that we have the controller_manager package installed,
OKこれで controller_manager パッケージがインストールされました
let's try building again.
では もう一度構築してみましょう
I'm still in the top level directories,
最上位ディレクトリから移動していないため
so I can just type catkin-make and hit Enter.
そのまま catkin_make と入力して Enter キーを押します
Awesome. So, it look like the build worked.
素晴らしい構築に成功したようです
Great. That wasn't so bad.
いいですね悪くないです
Now we can run some of the code from this package that we just cloned.
これで 今クローン作成したパッケージのコードを実行できるようになります